Finding aid for Media Resources Center (University of Michigan) Films and Videotapes, 1930s and 1948-1987
Bentley Historical Library
- Series S
  - Engineering Promotional Footage
    - Engineering Promo, [851831-S-11-13]; (Additional footage for College of Engineering promotional film. Includes transfer of 16mm film "The Link.")
      - Original:, 2-inch video #598
    - Engineering Promo, [851831-S-11-14]; (Additional footage for College of Engineering promotional film. Includes transfer of the 16mm film "Robots, Unigraphics, tapping the Source.")
      - Original:, 2-inch video #600
    - Engineering Promo, [851831-S-11-15]; (Additional footage for College of Engineering promotional film.)
      - Original:, 2-inch video #599
    - Engineering Promo, [851831-S-11-16]; (Additional footage for College of Engineering promotional film.)
      - Original:, 2-inch video #601
  - Engineering School Fund Raising, 1976; [851831-S-13]; (Program for use at meetings of UM Engineering Alumni. Three alums join Howe and Rugone in discussion of capital campaign to upgrade campus engineering facilities. Footage of old labs and North Campus sites. Fleming discusses development plans. Features: Robert Howe, UM-Eng.; Robben Fleming, UM-Pres.; Dave Rugone, UM-Eng.)
    - Original:, 16mm film, Pos. #3405 (also 3/4-inch tape B35-B38)
  - Fairlane Announcement, [851831-S-14]; (Footage of Henry Ford, II making transfer of Fairlane Mansion to the University of Michigan. Features: Harlan Hatcher, UM-Pres.; Henry Ford, II)
    - Original:, 1-inch video, b/w, sound, ca. 30:00, Tape #572
  - Ford Library Conference of the Presidency and Foreign Policy, [851831-S-16]; (Coverage of a conference held at the Gerald R. Ford Presidential Library on the presidency and foreign policy. (Three one-inch tapes, nos. 628-630.))
    - Original:, 2-inch video #628
  - Ford/UAW/SPH, [851831-S-17]; (Source footage for a program on the handling of caustic and hazardous material sponsored by Ford Motor Co., the United Auto Workers, and UM School of Public Health, includes footage from Ford's Rawsonville plant. (Three one-inch tapes, nos. 642-645.))
    - Original:, 2-inch video #642
  - Full Circle, [851831-S-18]
    - Original:, 2-inch video, Tape #536
  - G.R. Garrison Television Studio Dedication
    - G.R. Garrison Dedication, [851831-S-19-1]; (Footage of a "roast" of Garnet Garrison on the occasion of his retirement. Hazen Schumacher hosts, speakers include many current and former employees of the UM television studios. Features: Garnet Garrison, UM-Speech; Hazen Schumacher, UM-TVC)
      - Original:, cassette #M174
    - G.R. Garrison Dedication, [851831-S-19-2]; (Continues the "roast" of Garnet Garrison on the occasion of his retirement. Features: Garnet Garrsion, UM-Speech; Hazen Schumacher, UM-TVC)
      - Original:, cassette #M175
    - G.R. Garrison Dedication (Personal Messages To G.R.G.), [851831-S-20]; (Personal menages to Garnet Garrison from television center staff and friends on the occasion of his retirement.)
      - Original:, cassette #M173
  - Hazen's Campus Slide Show, [851831-S-24]; (Two-inch videotape of a slide show depicting University of Michigan campus buildings, personalities and events. Produced by Hazen Schumacher.)
    - Original:, 2-inch videotape
  - Jackson State Prison footage
    - Jackson State Prison, 1977; [851831-S-25-1]; (Footage shot at the State Prison of Southern Michigan in Jackson for use in the Series B program "Medicine Behind Bars." Includes pan shots of the prison grounds, mess hall, kitchen and other facilities, brief interviews with inmates and guards.)
      - Original:, cassette #B120
    - Jackson State Prison, 1977; [851831-S-25-2]; (Continues footage of Jackson State Prison.)
      - Original:, cassette #B121
    - Jackson State Prison, 1977; [851831-S-25-3]; (Continues footage of Jackson State Prison.)
      - Original:, cassette #B122
    - Jackson State Prison, 1977; [851831-S-25-4]; (Continues footage of Jackson State Prison.)
      - Original:, cassette #B123
  - M Capsule - University of Michigan, [851831-S-26]; (Raw footage for promotional film for the University of Michigan aimed at prospective students. For Office of Undergraduate Admission.)
    - Original:
    - Use copy:, DVD (Box 14)
  - Magazine Segments
    - Magazine Segments, [851831-S-27]; (Short filler segments produced for WDIV-TV. Some of these were later used in the Series B "Phenomenon" programs. (No. 549-553 are two inch tapes. No. 554-559 are one-inch tapes labeled "Masters," 560-662 are one-inch tapes, some possibly duplicates.))
      - Original:
    - Magazine Segments, [851831-S-28-1]; (These programs appear to be the same as the Series B "Phenomenon" programs.)
      - Original:
    - Magazine Segments, [851831-S-28-2]
      - Original:
    - Magazine Segments, [851831-S-28-3]
      - Original:
    - Magazine Segments, [851831-S-28-4]
      - Original:
    - Magazine Segments, [851831-S-28-5]
      - Original:
    - Magazine Segments, [851831-S-28-6]
      - Original:
    - Magazine Segments, [851831-S-28-7]
      - Original:
    - Magazine Segments, [851831-S-28-8]
      - Original:
    - Magazine Segments, [851831-S-28-9]
      - Original:
    - Magazine Segments, [851831-S-28-10]
      - Original:
    - Magazine Segments, [851831-S-28-11]
      - Original:
  - Michigan Media Christmas Show
    - Michigan Media Christmas Show, 1960-1963; [851831-S-34-1]; (Two-inch videotape of a Christmas show put on by members of the Michigan media staff. (Tape #537))
      - Original:
    - Michigan Media Christmas Show, 1964; [851831-S-34-2]; (Two-inch videotape of Christmas show put on by members of Michigan Media staff. (Tape #524))
      - Original:
    - Michigan Media Christmas Show, 1965; [851831-S-34-3]; (Two-inch videotape of Christmas show put on by members of Michigan Media staff. (Tape #525))
      - Original:, Pos. #957
    - Michigan Media Christmas Show, 1967; [851831-S-34-4]; (Two-inch videotape of Christmas show put on by members of Michigan Media staff. (Tape #526))
      - Original:
    - Michigan Media Christmas Show, 1968; [851831-S-34-5]; (Two-inch videotape of Christmas show put on by members of Michigan Media staff. (Tape #527))
      - Original:
    - Michigan Media Christmas Show, 1971; [851831-S-34-6]; (Two-inch videotape of Christmas show put on by members of Michigan Media staff. (Tape #528))
      - Original:
    - Michigan Media Christmas Show, 1972; [851831-S-34-7]; (Two-inch videotape of Christmas show put on by members of Michigan Media staff. (Tape #529))
      - Original:
    - Michigan Media Christmas Show, 1973; [851831-S-34-8]; (Two-inch videotape of Christmas show put on by members of Michigan Media staff. (Tape #530))
      - Original:
    - Michigan Media Christmas Show, 1974; [851831-S-34-9]; (Two-inch videotape of Christmas show put on by members of Michigan Media staff. (Tape #531))
      - Original:
    - Michigan Media Christmas Show, 1975; [851831-S-34-10]; (Two-inch videotape of Christmas show put on by members of Michigan Media staff. (Tape #532))
      - Original:
    - Michigan Media Christmas Show, 1976; [851831-S-34-11]; (Two-inch videotape of Christmas show put on by Michigan Media staff members. (Tape #533))
      - Original:
  - Michigan Media Live
    - Michigan Media Live, 1982; [851831-S-35-1]; (One-inch tape no. 621.)
      - Original:, 2-inch video #621
    - Michigan Media Live, 1982; [851831-S-35-2]; (One-inch tape no. 622.)
      - Original:, 2-inch video #622
    - Michigan Media Live, 1982; [851831-S-35-3]; (One-inch tape no. 623.)
      - Original:, 2-inch video #623
    - Michigan Media Live, 1982; [851831-S-35-4]; (One-inch tape no. 624)
      - Original:, 2-inch video #624
  - Music School Promo, [851831-S-36]; (Edited master for a UM School of Music promotional tape. (One-inch tape no. 617.))
    - Original:, 2-inch video #617
  - Office of Communications, 1987; [851831-S-39]; (Interviews with University of Michigan students. (One-inch tape no. 627.))
    - Original:, 2-inch video #627
  - President Fleming Inaugural Announcement, 1968; [851831-S-40]; (Two inch videotape of CBS(?) produced newsclip on the inauguration of Pres. Fleming, March 11, 1968. (Tape #569) Features: Robben Fleming, UM-Pres.)
    - Original:, 2-inch video, Tape #569
  - Robert Frost Live Remote From Hill Auditorium, [851831-S-42]; (Documentary footage of a lecture, poetry reading by Robert Frost. (This was produced for the MPATI series "Franklin to Frost." Duplication of this program is restricted. Obtain permission from MPATI and the Frost estate.) Features: Robert Frost)
    - Original:, 2-inch video, b/w, sound, 01:02:39, Tape #573
    - Use copy:, DVD (Box 14)
    - Streaming File:, 851831-S42.flv
  - Television Center Dedication Ceremony, 1974
    - Television Center Dedication Ceremony, 1974; [851831-S-46-1]; (Footage of Sept. 19, 1974 dedication ceremony at TVC's Argus Building facilities and of the symposium "Where is Television Going?" Sept. 19, 1974. Features: Garnett Garrison, UM-TVC; other TVC staff)
      - Original:, 2-inch video, ca. 30:00, Tape #565
    - Television Center Dedication Ceremony, 1974; [851831-S-46-2]; (Continues coverage of the TVC symposium.)
      - Original:, 2-inch video, ca. 30:00, Tape #566
    - Television Center Dedication Ceremony, 1974; [851831-S-46-3]; (Continues coverage of the TVC symposium.)
      - Original:, 2-inch video, ca. 30:00, Tape #567
    - Television Center Dedication Ceremony, 1974; [851831-S-46-4]; (Continues coverage of the TVC symposium.)
      - Original:, 2-inch video, ca. 30:00, Tape #565
  - Theodore Bikel Interview, 1987; [851831-S-47]; (Interview with singer/poet/actor Theodore Bikel. (One-inch tape no. 618.) Features: Theodore Bikel)
    - Original:, 2-inch video #618
  - Video Festival
    - Video Festival Promo, 1984; [851831-S-57]; (Unedited original footage and "A" and "B" rolls of promotional material for UM sponsored national student video festival. (Six one-inch tapes, nos. 605-611.))
      - Original:, 2-inch video #605
    - Video Festival Winners, 1985, [851831-S-58-1]; (Edited versions of winning entries in the UM sponsored national student video festival of 1985.)
      - Original:, 2-inch video #602
    - Video Festival Winners, 1985, [851831-S-58-2]; (Continues edited versions of winning entries in UM sponsored national student video festival.)
      - Original:, 2-inch video #603
    - Video Festival Winners, 1985, [851831-S-58-3]; (Continues edited versions of winning entries in UM sponsored national student video festival.)
      - Original:, 2-inch video #604
  - WWJ-TV Basketball Spots, 1977; [851831-S-59]; (Five promotional spots for the UM broadcast during half-time of UM basketball games. Include features on "Project Community," UM students, a tour of campus, women's sports, and a profile of basketball coach Johnny Orr. Features: Johnny Orr, UM-Athl.)
    - Original:, 2-inch tape #563.
  - Wallenberg Lecture
    - Part 1: Opening Luncheon, 1972; [851831-S-61-1]; (Documentary footage (b/w) of the first Wallenberg Lecture sponsored by the UM School of Architecture and Design, March 15-16, 1972. Includes footage of ceremonies opening the symposium and all lectures and discussions. (Two-inch videotape #574.) Features: William Haber, UM-Econ.; Leonard Eaton, UM-Arch.; Robben Fleming, UM-Pres.; Nicholas Pevsner)
      - Original:
      - Use copy:, DVD (Box 14)
      - Streaming File:, 851831-S61-1.flv
    - Part 2: Opening Luncheon, 1972; [851831-S-61-2]; (Opening luncheon/welcome of lecture, Malcomson introduces program, Fleming welcomes guests, Haber talks about Wallentberg, King talks about Wallenberg and establishing Wallenberg Fund Features: Malcomson, Reginald, UM-Arch, Fleming, Robben; Haber, William, UM-LSA; King, Saul; Slomovitz, Philip)
      - Original:, 2-inch video, b/w, sound, 00:07:27, Tape #574
      - Use copy:, DVD (Box 14)
      - Streaming File:, 851831-S61-2.flv
    - Part 3: Lecture, 1972; [851831-S-61-3]; (Malcomson introduces program, King discuses Wallneberg, Eaton introduces Pevsner, Pevsner lectures, Slomovitz, moves thanks to Pevsner Features: Malcomson,.Reginald, UM-Arch; Leonard Eaton, UM-Arch; King, Charles; Pevsner, Sir Nicholas; Slomovits, Philip, Detroit Jewish News)
      - Original:, 2-inch video, b/w, sound, 00:65:45, Tape #576
      - Use copy:, DVD (Box 14)
      - Streaming File:, 851831-S61-3.flv
    - Part 4: Lecture, 1972; [851831-S-61-4]; (Continues coverage of the Wallenberg Lecture symposium. (duplicate of last 10 minutes of tape # 3))
      - Original:, 2-inch video, b/w, sound, 00:10:53, Tape #577
      - Use copy:, DVD (Box 14)
      - Streaming File:, 851831-S61-4.flv
    - Part 5: Symposium, 1972; [851831-S-61-5]; (Symposium: Introduction and remarks by panelists, question and answers. Features: Eaton, Leonard, UM-Arch; Birkerts, Gunnar, UM-Arch; Crees, Walter- U of Ill.; Pevsner, Sir Nicholas)
      - Original:, 2-inch video, b/w, sound, 00:00:59:46, Tape #578
      - Use copy:, DVD (Box 14)
      - Streaming File:, 851831-S61-5.flv
    - Wallenberg Lecture, 1972, [851831-S-61-6]; (Continues coverage of the Wallenberg Lecture symposium.: questions and answers (seems to be duplicate of part 5) Features: Eaton, Leonard, UM-Arch; Birkerts, Gunnar, UM-Arch; Crees, Walrer- U of Ill.; Pevsner, Sir Nicholas)
      - Original:, 2-inch video, b/w, sound, 00:59:47, Tape #579
      - Use copy:, DVD (Box 14)
      - Streaming File:, 851831-S61-6.flv
    - Wallenberg Lecture, 1972, [851831-S-61-7]; (Continues coverage of the Wallenberg Lecture symposium. (Two-inch videotape #580.) Features: Eaton, Leonard, UM-Arch; Birkerts, Gunnar, UM-Arch; Crees, Walrer- U of Ill.; Pevsner, Sir Nicholas)
      - Original:, 2-inch video, b/w, sound, 00:10:07, Tape #580
      - Use copy:, DVD (Box 14)
      - Streaming File:, 851831-S61-7.flv
  - In Honor of Raoul Wallenberg, 1972; [851831-S-62]; (Highlights of the first Wallenberg lecture, include statements by William Haber, Robben Fleming, and Leonard Eaton and excerpts from the address of architectural historian Nicholas Pevsner. (Film used as promotional, fund raising program for the Wallenberg Lecture endowment campaign.) Features: Haber, William, Fleming, Robben UM-Pres.; Leif Leifland, Swedish Ambassador; King, Saul, Pevsner Nicholas)
    - Original:, 2-inc
    - Use copy:, DVD (Box 14)
    - Streaming File:
  - We Came to Ann Arbor, 1978; [851831-S-63]; (An Alumni Association sponsored film featuring scenes from UM campus and Ann Arbor including footage from 1930s, Interviews with alumni who have returned to campus.)
    - Original:, 16mm film, color, sound, 00:59:30, Pos. #3557
    - Use copy:, DVD (Box 14)
    - Streaming File:, 851831-S63.flv
  - What We Have: TLC, [851831-S-64]; (A dramatized documentary about the "Teaching Learning Communities" program in which older people work with students at Bach Elementary School in Ann Arbor, Michigan. Features: Carol Tice; Ann Batchelder)
    - Original:, cassette, M179
  - Willow Run Footage for PSA, 1983; [851831-S-66]; (Two one-inch tapes, nos. 640-641.)
    - Original:, 2-inch video #640
  - Women in the 1930s at the University of Michigan, [851831-S-67]; (Film on women students at UM in the 1930s shows women in classroom, dormitory and social settings. Some original 1930s footage and some apparently staged shots. Shots of campus and town. (Tape #570 is a duplicate 2 inch master, use for copying.))
    - Original:, 1-inch videotape, color, silent, 00:37:22, Tape # 570
    - Use copy:, DVD (Box 14)
    - Streaming file:, 851831-S67.flv
  - Women in the 1930s at the University of Michigan, 1938; [851831-S-71]; (Film on women students at UM in the 1930s shows women in classroom, dormitory and social settings. Some original 1930s footage and some apparently staged shots. Shots of campus and town. (This is apparently a duplicate 1-inch-tape, includes added title cards and countdown))
    - Original:, 1-inch video "duplicate" of S-67, color, silent, 00:38:16, Tape #571
    - Use copy:, DVD (Box 14)
  - Your Own Home Town: Ann Arbor, Michigan, 1936; [851831-S-70]; (Newsreel film (b/w, silent) on Ann Arbor, footage of UM administrators and faculty, football team and coaches, Ann Arbor officials, AA businesses and their employees including Klines dept. store, Hutzel plumbing, Dhu Varren Farms, Features: Alexander Ruthven, Edward H. Krause, Mortimer Cooley, Herbert C. Sadler, Harry Kipke)
    - Original:, 16mm film, b/w silent, 00:18:30, Pos. #283, 2-inch video #568
    - Use copy:, DVD (Box 14)
    - Streaming File:, 851831-S70.flv
  - Television Center History, [851831-S-74]; (Video history of the UM-Television Center includes historic photographs, shots of studios and equipment, and shots of staff. Made at time of dedication on new studio in Argus Building.)
    - Original:, videocassette #B135
  - Here Comes The, 1951; [851831-S-72]; (Film produced by RKO-Pathe studios on the University of Michigan Marching Band Features: Marching Band)
    - Original:, 16mm film, b/w sound, 00:15:52, Pos. #72
    - Use copy:, DVD (Box 14)
    - Streaming File:, 851831-S72.flv
  - You and Youth and I, [851831-S-73]; (Original 16mm film by Alumnae Association on women students at UM in the 1930s shows women in classroom, dormitory and social settings. Some original 1930s footage and some apparently staged shots. Shots of campus and town. (2-inch tape #571 dubbed from the film.) (Film includes shots from Arboretum at end))
    - Original:, 16mm film, color, silent, 0:15:51 @ 18fps.
    - Use copy:, DVD (Box 14)
    - Streaming File:
  - Law School Project, [851831-S-75]; (Unedited footage and a dubbing master for a UM Law School promotion and recruiting project. (Three one-inch tapes, nos. 614-616.))
    - Original:, 2-inch video #614-616
- Series T, Telecourses
  Series T, University of Michigan Telecourses broadcast on the original Television Hour, 1950/51-1953/54. The "telecourses" (a term coined by the Television Center) as 2- minute, for-credit classes broadcast from the WWJ studio in Detroit. IN the fall of 1952 the Telecourse was expanded to a half- hour format, but university credit was no longer offered. It was not until 1954 that the telecourses were recorded on kinescope film. Only a portion of the recorded telecourses have survived, in some cases only a single segment of a program. A selection of the films were digitized in 2009.
  - American Business, (What Makes Prosperity.; Segments of a 7 part series on the story of the past and present of our great, expanding economy. A study of why American business conditions will lead this country to continuing prosperity. Features: Philip Wernette, UM-Bus.)
    - What Makes Prosperity, 1954; [851831-T-1-1]; (What Makes Prosperity.; Segments of a 7 part series on the story of the past and present of our great, expanding economy. A study of why American business conditions will lead this country to continuing prosperity. Features: Philip Wernette, UM-Bus.)
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope, bw, sound, 30:00, Pos. #1765
    - How Dangerous Is Inflation?, 1954; [851831-T-1-2]; (How Dangerous is Inflation?; Segment of a 7 part series on the American economy. A discussion of the nature of inflation and its effect upon our economy. Features: Philip Wernette, UM-Bus.)
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope, bw, sound, 30:00, Pos. #1226
  - Engineering: Building the Modern World, (15 part telecourse featuring demonstrations by UM engineers of accomplishments of our mechanical age.)
    - Why Metals Are Strong, 1954; [851831-T-2-10]; (Segment of a 15 part telecourse featuring demonstrations by UM engineers of accomplishments of our mechanical age. A discussion of the process involved in strengthening metals by changing the graphic flakes into balls. Features: Richard Flinn, UM-Eng.)
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope, bw, sound, 29:33, Pos. #1674
      - Use copy:, DVD (Box 14)
      - Streaming File:, 851831-T2-10.flv
  - Fish and Fishing: In Recreation and Commerce, (An 8 part telecourse about the habits and harvesting of fish in our lakes, stream and ocean waters.)
    - Conservation, 1954; [851831-T-3-8]; (This program points out the way to bigger fish and better fishing for American sport fishermen. Features: Karl Lagler, UM-SNR; J.W. Leonard)
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope, bw, sound, 16:53, Pos. #1682
      - Use copy:, DVD (Box 14)
      - Streaming File:, 851831-T3-8.flv
  - Man in His World: Human Biology, (Fifteen part telecourse on human biology. This was the first telecourse the Television Center offered.)
    - The Muscular and Skeletal Systems, 1950; [851831-T-4-7]; (Part 7 of a 15 part telecourse on human biology. This segment examines the structure and functioning of the skeletal and muscular systems. Features: Karl Lagler, UM-SNR, Carl Badgley, UM-Med.)
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope, bw, sound, 30:00, Pos. #1680
  - Man in His World: Modern Physics, (Fifteen part telecourse exploring the principles and applications of modern physics.)
    - Measurement of Time, 1953; [851831-T-4-12]; (Part 12 of a 15 part telecourse exploring the principles and applications of modern physics. This program examines the use of radioactive carbon in dating prehistoric objects. Features: Ernest F. Barker, UM-Physics)
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope, bw, sound, 30:00, Pos. #1667
  - Political Parties, (Thirteen part telecourse dealing with the role of political parties in our democratic system.)
    - Nature and Functions, 1954; [851831-T-5-1]; (This program looks into American history and gives a frank assessment of the present job of the Democratic and Republican Parties. Features: Samuel Eldersveld, UM-Pol.)
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope, bw, sound, 29:21, Pos. #1273
      - Use copy:, DVD (Box 14)
      - Streaming File:, 851831-T5-1.flv
    - Features of American Parties, 1954; [851831-T-5-2]; (Looks at reasons why we have never had a successful third party and questions whether sectionalism is a healthy element in our party system. Features: Samuel Elderveld, UM-Pol.; George Peek, UM-Pol.)
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope, bw, sound, 30:0
    - Parties in Foreign Countries, 1954; [851831-T-5-3]; (A look at U.S. parties in contrast to the party systems of Germany, Turkey, and Japan. Features: Robert Ward, UM-Pol.; Henry Bretton, UM-Pol.; Marbury Efimanco, UM-Pol.)
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope, bw, sound, 29:18, Pos. #1272
      - Use copy:, DVD (Box 14)
      - Streaming File:, 851831-T5-3.flv
    - Party Organization, 1954; [851831-T-5-4]; (Democratic National Committeewoman from Michigan and chairman of the Michigan Republican State Central Committee discuss where the power lies in political parties and how much voice voters have in party affairs. Features: Samuel Eldersveld, UM-Pol.; Margaret Price; John Feikens)
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope, bw, sound, 29:18, Pos. #1274
      - Use copy:, DVD (Box 14)
      - Streaming File:, 851831-T5-4.flv
    - Nominating the Candidates, 1954; [851831-T-5-5]; (A comparison of the Russian and U.S. nominating systems, with a dramatic presentation of the primary voting procedure. Features: Samuel Eldersveld, UM-Pol.)
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope, bw, sound, 29:20, Pos. #1277
      - Use copy:, DVD (Box 14)
      - Streaming File:, 0851831-T5-5.flv
    - Presidential Nominations, 1954; [851831-T-5-6]; (A close study of the battles involved in the pre-convention and convention period of presidential nominations. Features: Samuel Eldersveld, UM-Pol.)
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope, bw, sound, 29:18, Pos. #1280
      - Use copy:, DVD (Box 14)
      - Streaming File:, 851831-T5-6.flv
    - Campaign Strategy, 1954; [851831-T-5-7]; (An analysis of controversial aspects of our political campaigns, with a focus on the 1952 election, includes a dramatized campaign strategy meeting. Features: Samuel Eldersveld, UM-Pol.)